[
    {
        "front": "こちら",
        "back": "I am (here is) (Polite)",
        "chapter": "N5 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "こちらこそ",
        "back": "Same here",
        "chapter": "N5 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "じょうず",
        "back": "Good at\n<adj.>",
        "chapter": "N5 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "へた",
        "back": "Not good at",
        "chapter": "N5 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "すき",
        "back": "Like, love",
        "chapter": "N5 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "きらい",
        "back": "Dislike",
        "chapter": "N5 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "でわ/じゃ",
        "back": "Well then",
        "chapter": "N5 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "ぎんこう こうざ",
        "back": "Bank Account",
        "chapter": "N5 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "しりょう",
        "back": "Documents",
        "chapter": "N5 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "せつめい",
        "back": "Explanation",
        "chapter": "N5 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "こたえ",
        "back": "Answer, Reply",
        "chapter": "N5 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちょっと",
        "back": "Little bit",
        "chapter": "N5 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "だします",
        "back": "To Submit",
        "chapter": "N5 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "まだ",
        "back": "Still, yet",
        "chapter": "N5 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "もんだい",
        "back": "Problem",
        "chapter": "N5 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "しつもん",
        "back": "Question",
        "chapter": "N5 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "ほか",
        "back": "Other",
        "chapter": "N5 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "あまり",
        "back": "Not that much",
        "chapter": "N5 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "ひ",
        "back": "Day",
        "chapter": "N5 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "まだまだ",
        "back": "\"not yet\"",
        "chapter": "N5 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "えんぴつ",
        "back": "Pencil",
        "chapter": "N5 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "どうして",
        "back": "Why",
        "chapter": "N5 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "え",
        "back": "Painting",
        "chapter": "N5 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "から",
        "back": "Therefore",
        "chapter": "N5 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "ぜんぜん",
        "back": "Not at all",
        "chapter": "N5 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "こまかい",
        "back": "Change",
        "chapter": "N5 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "おかね",
        "back": "Money",
        "chapter": "N5 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "いけない",
        "back": "Can’t go",
        "chapter": "N5 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "ばんせん",
        "back": "Platform",
        "chapter": "N5 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "つぎ",
        "back": "Next",
        "chapter": "N5 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "ふつう",
        "back": "Local",
        "chapter": "N5 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "としょかん",
        "back": "Library",
        "chapter": "N5 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "しょうがっこう",
        "back": "Primary School",
        "chapter": "N5 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "きょうかい",
        "back": "Church",
        "chapter": "N5 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちゅうがっこう",
        "back": "Middle School",
        "chapter": "N5 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "しやくしょ",
        "back": "City Hall",
        "chapter": "N5 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "びょういん",
        "back": "Hospital",
        "chapter": "N5 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "こうしょう",
        "back": "Factory",
        "chapter": "N5 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "ゆうびんきょく",
        "back": "Post Office",
        "chapter": "N5 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "じんじゃ",
        "back": "Temple",
        "chapter": "N5 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "はさみ",
        "back": "Scissors",
        "chapter": "N5 C8"
    },
    {
        "front": "かわ",
        "back": "River",
        "chapter": "N5 C8"
    }
]